We are joined by Kid and I did see a video not too long ago y'all was doing the kid and play dance that was fun to watch.
I'm glad you brought that up because you know it's interesting because one of the things I've been trying to get us to do and we're gonna do is change the record that we do that kick step to because the one we do it to you do that kick step slow so it looks like we're not able to do the kick step.
So when you watch when you watch house party the movie we're doing it to full forces ain't my type of height which is a more is a faster speed in order for us to do it in that pace but to do it to roll it with Kid and play it's a slower tempo so it makes it like we're grandpaing through it you know and it's not true.
I don't know if we want to speed it up just yet. I got brand new hip and I'm trying to keep it.
And then another thing that we're going to add that I'm talking Kid into I want to do it blindfolded.
That's a really that's a really bad idea that is really.
No but see what makes it fun is if we hit or miss either way it's fun you know the audience will still laugh along with us they'll get it but if we get it you know what I'm saying.
It'll go viral before we leave the stage.
You see when Beyonce fell it went viral before she hit the ground.
You got to be careful.